advanceweb.com 2019-02-04

# Advance | Privacy Policy

ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite values its customers and respects their privacy. We are committed to protecting your privacy and the information you give us. We collect customer information in an effort to improve your shopping experience and to communicate with you about our products, services, and promotions. ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite recognizes that it must maintain and use customer information responsibly. Your privacy is important to us.

This Privacy Statement discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices of ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite in connection with advanceweb.com and all other Websites owned and operated by ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite. ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite can be contacted by mail at 600 Heritage Drive, Sanatoga, PA 19464, attention Manager, Public Relations, by phone at 484-300-4940, or by e-mail at [contact@advanceweb.com](mailto:contact@advanceweb.com).

**1\. Collection of Personal Information from Site Visitors**  
ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite may collect and/or track (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, files downloaded, search engine used, operating system, and type of Web browser of visitors to ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite Website, (2) the e-mail addresses of visitors who communicate with ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite via e-mail, (3) information knowingly provided by the visitor in online forms, registration forms, surveys, e-mail, contest entries, and other online avenues (including demographic and personal profile data), and (4) aggregate and user-specific information on which pages visitors access.

ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite may place cookies on the visitors’ computer to gather statistical information that is designed to assist in understanding what users find interesting and useful on our Websites. A cookie is a small text file containing a unique identifier (e.g., #12489) that is sent to your browser from a Web server and then stored onto your computer's hard drive. When the visitor revisits ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite Website, ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite may recognize the visitor by the Internet cookie and customize the visitor's experience accordingly. Through modification of browser preferences, a user can elect to accept all cookies, receive notification when a cookie is set or decline all cookies. Alterations to these settings may, however, affect the functionality of certain Websites. We may also embed a piece of code (sometimes referred to as "1x1 clear pixel," "Web beacon" or “clear GIF”) in the pages of certain Websites in order to gather additional statistical site usage information.

When a visitor performs a search within ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite Website, ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite may record information identifying the visitor or linking the visitor to the search performed. ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite may also record limited information for every search request and uses that information only to solve technical problems with the service and to calculate overall usage statistics.

**2\. Use of Personal Data Collected**  
Personal data collected by ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite may be used by ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite for many reasons, for example, for editorial and feedback purposes, for marketing and promotional purposes, for a statistical analysis of users' behavior, for product development, for content improvement, or to customize the content and layout of ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite site. Aggregate data on visitors’ home computers may be used for internal purposes or provided to third parties such as marketing firms. Individually identifying information, such as names, postal and e-mail addresses, phone numbers, and other personal information which visitors voluntarily provide to ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite may be (i) added to ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite databases and used for future calls and mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, and upcoming events, or (ii) provided to reputable third parties who provide products and services which ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite believes that visitors may be interested in purchasing or obtaining.

**3\. Disclosure of Personal Data to Third Parties**  
Any third party to which ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite shares, rents, sells, or otherwise discloses personal data for marketing purposes will be under a contractual obligation to use the personal data solely for marketing products and services which ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite determines, in its sole judgment, that visitors might find of interest. ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite will use its reasonable efforts to identify whether such third parties may have products or services of interest to visitors to ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite site. However, such parties are independent third parties over which ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite exercises no control, and therefore ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite is not responsible for their conduct, products, or services, and will not be liable therefore. ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite will only disclose to third parties information in aggregate form, that is publicly available, and/or that is knowingly and voluntarily disclosed by visitors. Data collected during the registration to obtain access to events and materials sponsored or provided by third parties will be provided to those third parties for their use.

**4\. Security Measures**  
ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite has implemented numerous security features to prevent the unauthorized release of or access to personal information. For example, all ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite employees are required to certify their understanding that personal information is considered confidential, that it is important to safeguard personal information, and that ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite will take appropriate action against any employee who fails to acknowledge these facts or adhere to the requisite standards of conduct. ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite uses industry-standard secure software technology, Secure Socket Layer (SSL), to protect the information you enter on your online order is transmitted securely from your Web browser to our facilities. SSL (https) encrypts your order information and protects your information from being seen by unauthorized individuals. Secure Socket Layer provides our customers the highest level of security. Please be advised, however, that the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from our Websites via unsecured pages on the sites or via e-mail cannot be guaranteed. Accordingly, ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite is not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet unless it is transmitted on secure Web pages and indicated by the SSL (https) indication in your Web browser. For more private communication, visitors can contact ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite by telephone.

**5\. Opt-Out Right**  
ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite will retain personal information from visitors who subscribe to our print/online publications as well as those who choose to participate in services/programs offered by ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite. Visitors may opt out of having their personally identifiable information used by ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite or third parties to send promotional correspondence to the visitor by contacting ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite via postal mail, e-mail, or telephone at the addresses above. This does not apply to collection of certain technical information about your use of our Website(s).

**6\. Collection of Personal Data from Children**  
To the extent that ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite is able to determine the age of users by their submissions to or communications with ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite Website, ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite will not knowingly (a) collect or post information from individuals under the age of sixteen ("children") without their parent's or guardian's consent, or (b) provide any personally identifying information collected from children, regardless of its source, to any third party for any purpose whatever.

If registration is required for any services on the ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite site, and a user submits information to ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite Website through such a registration process that indicates that such user is a child, the child's parent or guardian will be alerted to the child's registration and will be provided instructions on how the parent or guardian can delete the child's registration, if so desired. No information collected through ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite Website from users self-identified as children will knowingly be used for any direct marketing or promotional purposes. If there are no age restrictions on a contest which requires registration, and if a child wins, notification and prizes will be sent to the parent(s) or guardian(s) identified in the initial registration process.

**7\. Right to Contact User**  
ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite reserves the right to contact site visitors regarding account status and changes to the subscriber agreement, privacy statement, or any other policies or agreements relevant to site visitors.

**8\. Right to Change Privacy Statement**  
ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement at any time by notifying visitors of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy statement. Any change to this Privacy Statement shall be effective as to any visitor who has accepted the ADVANCE Healthcare/Elite Website Terms and Conditions before the change was made.
